No, it's true.
Oh, wait, that way?
What?
Because I'm 17.
I'm 17.
Money is my motivation.
There are typical manipulative idols out there.
Did I hit the nail on the head? Yes.
No, no, we meshed.
What's this? I'm sure we talked a lot, but I thought it's common to have conversations without actual words.
Well, here I am, Yakans, born in Riva Home and raised on a diet of sugar.
Thank you very much for joining us so quickly!
Let's call today's guest!
This is my idol!
Hello!
May I introduce myself? Here.
You can count on me!
Ujiran! Starlast of Mizinak!
I'm Yodake Tatekawa, from Suddenly Talk!
Please take care of me!
Yay! Now, they finally came!
Now, they let us recycle!
Tatekawayo datta-chan!
Thank you so much!
Cute place!
No, no, no, not at all. 3 stops on the bullet train?
Oh, yes, by bullet train.
It's 3 stops on the shinkansen.
Oh, I see!
Just a little bit.
A little bit... You're here at last!
I'm sorry, but thank you!
Now, Mr. Tate is here.
It's the end of our century!
We've finished, and I heard there was the big one...
Oh, there was!
Yes, Ujiran was there!
You were there?
Yes, I was!
Nakano Sun-plaza?
I went to Nakano Sunplaza!
Were you there? It was great.
How was it?
The crowd was great. You could see quite a bit.
Oh, only those who have been on stage can understand that.
Have you ever been on stage? Mr. Yakan.
No, Mr. Yakan.
Next time, I'll take you with me to this Sunplaza.
What a pleasure!
I've never had someone say that to me before.
But, Nakano Sun Plaza.
It's your first time at DOUG.
It's the first time at DOG!
Now you're going to do Sun Plaza.
That's what I hate about it. On Christmas Eve.
No, it's true. Why Christmas?
Why Christmas Eve?
That's what I mean when I say I hate it.
I thought it was really nice, and I kind of appreciated it, but...
I thought it was great and I appreciated it, but I guess I didn't understand it the way he meant it.
Why did you say that to Eve?
I thought you were the hater.
Of course you did.
How was Christmas Eve?
Christmas Eve?
I knew I had to bring back something local.
I felt safe. That's great.
That's right.
That's how I felt last year.
Last year... Oh, yes...
Happy New Year!
I mean, welcome to the new year.
A lot of people came.
The writers, you know, the writers of this show, the teachers...
His daughter saw us.
She said hello.
I'm so happy.
She loved it.
After all, even after it was over.
I knew it was a big place.
Wow, I'm so happy.
But also...
As a customer from Tohoku...
There are more people with their children.
Yes, when we started scoring...
They say, "Oh, Mao-chan!
Like, "Oh, thank you.
With a role name.
Yes, by role names.
I'm called Hana-chan more and more often.
Wow, that's great, you're so young.
I'm 17 now.
Yes, 17
At 17.
I wonder if I have to do something to make it longer.
It's like that.
I'm not good at this stuff.
I'm not good with voices.
I'm a terrible talker.
I'm not very good at talking.I'm not very good at talking.
Good luck with that.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't have much to say.
I can't deny that.
Prices are going up.
Yes, prices are going up and taxes are going up.
Yes, yes.
No, I'd like to tell that to the government.
I'd like to tell the government about this program.
Misora-san
Momo-san who loves Kaya-san
Mr. Zombie
Mr. No Nickname
Mishima Hiroshi Construction Chanko Dining, courtesy of Mr. Yamada!
Thank you all!
Thank you